<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Defs>
  <RulePackDef>
    <defName>RR_Album_DescRulePack</defName>
    <rulePack>
      <rulesStrings>

        <!-- ROOTS -->
        <li>art_description->[desc_root]</li>
        <li>r_art_description->[desc_root]</li>

        <!-- Choose either general or genre-tailored -->
        <li>desc_root->[desc_common]</li>
        <li>desc_root->[desc_by_genre]</li>

        <!-- General 3–5 sentence blurbs -->
        <li>desc_common->Tracked on simple gear, these pieces move in small steps. The set keeps rough edges and room hum by choice. Phrases return until they lock. It is steady material for long work and late rest.</li>
        <li>desc_common->Assembled after hours, the record favors patience over flash. You can hear switches, fans, and hands. Themes shift slightly each pass. It stays useful at low volume and honest at any hour.</li>
        <li>desc_common->Short ideas are worked like parts on a bench. Imperfections mark time, not failure. Lines repeat, drift, and settle. The result is plain and durable, made to carry through a shift.</li>
        <li>desc_common->Built from loops and simple counterlines, it documents a room as much as a performance. Nothing rushes. Over minutes, small changes gather weight. It is music that helps work get done.</li>

        <!-- GENRE ROUTER: pick one of many genre branches -->
        <li>desc_by_genre->[g_ambient]</li>
        <li>desc_by_genre->[g_folk]</li>
        <li>desc_by_genre->[g_rock]</li>
        <li>desc_by_genre->[g_jazz]</li>
        <li>desc_by_genre->[g_noise]</li>
        <li>desc_by_genre->[g_synth]</li>
        <li>desc_by_genre->[g_field]</li>
        <li>desc_by_genre->[g_analog]</li>
        <li>desc_by_genre->[g_minimal]</li>
        <li>desc_by_genre->[g_industrial]</li>
        <li>desc_by_genre->[g_piano]</li>
        <li>desc_by_genre->[g_country]</li>
        <li>desc_by_genre->[g_blues]</li>
        <li>desc_by_genre->[g_orchestral]</li>
        <li>desc_by_genre->[g_choral]</li>
        <li>desc_by_genre->[g_metal]</li>
        <li>desc_by_genre->[g_dub]</li>
        <li>desc_by_genre->[g_pop]</li>
        <li>desc_by_genre->[g_tribal]</li>
        <li>desc_by_genre->[g_psyche]</li>
        <li>desc_by_genre->[g_electronic]</li>

        <!-- AMBIENT -->
        <li>g_ambient->[g_ambient_intro] [g_ambient_body] [g_ambient_tail]</li>
        <li>g_ambient_intro->Layers of soft tone drift without a hard center.</li>
        <li>g_ambient_body->Air, hiss, and slow pads form long shapes that sit well under work.</li>
        <li>g_ambient_tail->Nothing demands attention; it keeps space open and steady.</li>

        <!-- FOLK -->
        <li>g_folk->[g_folk_intro] [g_folk_body] [g_folk_tail]</li>
        <li>g_folk_intro->Small string parts and close mics keep things plain.</li>
        <li>g_folk_body->Phrases repeat like work songs; time shows in the take.</li>
        <li>g_folk_tail->It is modest, warm, and built to last.</li>

        <!-- ROCK -->
        <li>g_rock->[g_rock_intro] [g_rock_body] [g_rock_tail]</li>
        <li>g_rock_intro->Guitars and drums speak in short, sturdy figures.</li>
        <li>g_rock_body->Riffs return with small shifts; grit stays in the print.</li>
        <li>g_rock_tail->It trades polish for drive and keeps moving weight.</li>

        <!-- JAZZ -->
        <li>g_jazz->[g_jazz_intro] [g_jazz_body] [g_jazz_tail]</li>
        <li>g_jazz_intro->A small group works simple heads and leaves room to answer.</li>
        <li>g_jazz_body->Brushes, upright, and clear chords hold the frame.</li>
        <li>g_jazz_tail->It listens hard, speaks brief, and keeps time like a tool.</li>

        <!-- NOISE -->
        <li>g_noise->[g_noise_intro] [g_noise_body] [g_noise_tail]</li>
        <li>g_noise_intro->Contact buzz, feedback bloom, and tape wear make the core.</li>
        <li>g_noise_body->Texture beats tune; edges are part of the plan.</li>
        <li>g_noise_tail->Heavy but honest, best at modest volume over long spans.</li>

        <!-- SYNTH -->
        <li>g_synth->[g_synth_intro] [g_synth_body] [g_synth_tail]</li>
        <li>g_synth_intro->Analog lines tick against square bass and simple clocks.</li>
        <li>g_synth_body->Sequences change in inches, leaving room to think.</li>
        <li>g_synth_tail->Clear, repeatable, and tuned for late shifts.</li>

        <!-- FIELD -->
        <li>g_field->[g_field_intro] [g_field_body] [g_field_tail]</li>
        <li>g_field_intro->Rooms, yards, and crossings appear as tone and pattern.</li>
        <li>g_field_body->Boot steps, far engines, and wire hum thread through short motifs.</li>
        <li>g_field_tail->It reads like a map: direct, patient, and useful.</li>

        <!-- ANALOG -->
        <li>g_analog->[g_analog_intro] [g_analog_body] [g_analog_tail]</li>
        <li>g_analog_intro->Reel-to-reel print, hiss intact, anchors the sound.</li>
        <li>g_analog_body->Manual punch-ins and slow fades mark each pass.</li>
        <li>g_analog_tail->The result feels worked, not polished, and holds up well.</li>

        <!-- MINIMAL -->
        <li>g_minimal->[g_minimal_intro] [g_minimal_body] [g_minimal_tail]</li>
        <li>g_minimal_intro->Few voices, clear roles, nothing extra.</li>
        <li>g_minimal_body->Small cells repeat and phase until they fit by feel.</li>
        <li>g_minimal_tail->It is light on surface and heavy on function.</li>

        <!-- INDUSTRIAL -->
        <li>g_industrial->[g_industrial_intro] [g_industrial_body] [g_industrial_tail]</li>
        <li>g_industrial_intro->Metal hits, motor thrum, and relay chatter drive the meter.</li>
        <li>g_industrial_body->Rhythms come from tools and fans as much as drums.</li>
        <li>g_industrial_tail->It moves like a line shift and stops clean.</li>

        <!-- PIANO -->
        <li>g_piano->[g_piano_intro] [g_piano_body] [g_piano_tail]</li>
        <li>g_piano_intro->Unadorned piano sketches set simple shapes.</li>
        <li>g_piano_body->Pedal noise and wood speak between notes.</li>
        <li>g_piano_tail->It is clear and calm, built for focus.</li>

        <!-- COUNTRY -->
        <li>g_country->[g_country_intro] [g_country_body] [g_country_tail]</li>
        <li>g_country_intro->Clean guitar, small kit, and plain voice mark the frame.</li>
        <li>g_country_body->Chords turn slow, lines walk steady.</li>
        <li>g_country_tail->It keeps good time and better company.</li>

        <!-- BLUES -->
        <li>g_blues->[g_blues_intro] [g_blues_body] [g_blues_tail]</li>
        <li>g_blues_intro->Twelve-bar shapes and bent notes carry the load.</li>
        <li>g_blues_body->Room sound and finger noise stay in the mix.</li>
        <li>g_blues_tail->It keeps the light on through a long night.</li>

        <!-- ORCHESTRAL -->
        <li>g_orchestral->[g_orchestral_intro] [g_orchestral_body] [g_orchestral_tail]</li>
        <li>g_orchestral_intro->Small ensemble parts stack into firm lines.</li>
        <li>g_orchestral_body->Low brass and strings trade weight and air.</li>
        <li>g_orchestral_tail->It speaks broad and keeps shape at low volume.</li>

        <!-- CHORAL -->
        <li>g_choral->[g_choral_intro] [g_choral_body] [g_choral_tail]</li>
        <li>g_choral_intro->Simple voices in unison open the door.</li>
        <li>g_choral_body->Close harmonies shift by hand, not grid.</li>
        <li>g_choral_tail->It settles like breath in a cool room.</li>

        <!-- METAL -->
        <li>g_metal->[g_metal_intro] [g_metal_body] [g_metal_tail]</li>
        <li>g_metal_intro->Low tuned guitars and tight kicks set the plate.</li>
        <li>g_metal_body->Riffs lock to the grid, then grind against it.</li>
        <li>g_metal_tail->It is heavy, dry, and to the point.</li>

        <!-- DUB -->
        <li>g_dub->[g_dub_intro] [g_dub_body] [g_dub_tail]</li>
        <li>g_dub_intro->Bass lines roll under wide space and delay.</li>
        <li>g_dub_body->Parts drop in and out like lights on a board.</li>
        <li>g_dub_tail->It breathes easy and warms the room.</li>

        <!-- POP -->
        <li>g_pop->[g_pop_intro] [g_pop_body] [g_pop_tail]</li>
        <li>g_pop_intro->Short hooks land quick and stay.</li>
        <li>g_pop_body->Clean drums and clear keys keep the center bright.</li>
        <li>g_pop_tail->It is light, neat, and made to repeat.</li>

        <!-- TRIBAL -->
        <li>g_tribal->[g_tribal_intro] [g_tribal_body] [g_tribal_tail]</li>
        <li>g_tribal_intro->Hand drums and call lines build the frame.</li>
        <li>g_tribal_body->Patterns circle and lock in layers.</li>
        <li>g_tribal_tail->It feels lived in and moves the floor.</li>

        <!-- PSYCHE -->
        <li>g_psyche->[g_psyche_intro] [g_psyche_body] [g_psyche_tail]</li>
        <li>g_psyche_intro->Long forms drift through delay and gentle fuzz.</li>
        <li>g_psyche_body->Motifs dissolve and return like a slow tide.</li>
        <li>g_psyche_tail->It aims wide and lands soft.</li>

        <!-- ELECTRONIC -->
        <li>g_electronic->[g_electronic_intro] [g_electronic_body] [g_electronic_tail]</li>
        <li>g_electronic_intro->Drum machines and small synths mark the grid.</li>
        <li>g_electronic_body->Clocks tick, filters open, parts shift in steps.</li>
        <li>g_electronic_tail->It stays clean and repeatable, fit for long focus.</li>

      </rulesStrings>
    </rulePack>
  </RulePackDef>
</Defs>
